Name:                                                  php-apache-hpa
Namespace:                                             app
Labels:                                                <none>
Annotations:                                           <none>
CreationTimestamp:                                     Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:17:37 -0300
Reference:                                             Deployment/php-apache
Metrics:                                               ( current / target )
  resource cpu on pods  (as a percentage of request):  0% (1m) / 50%
Min replicas:                                          1
Max replicas:                                          10
Deployment pods:                                       1 current / 1 desired
Conditions:
  Type            Status  Reason            Message
  ----            ------  ------            -------
  AbleToScale     True    ReadyForNewScale  recommended size matches current size
  ScalingActive   True    ValidMetricFound  the HPA was able to successfully calculate a replica count from cpu resource utilization (percentage of request)
  ScalingLimited  True    TooFewReplicas    the desired replica count is less than the minimum replica count
Events:
  Type     Reason                        Age   From                       Message
  ----     ------                        ----  ----                       -------
  Warning  FailedGetResourceMetric       15m   horizontal-pod-autoscaler  failed to get cpu utilization: unable to get metrics for resource cpu: no metrics returned from resource metrics API
  Warning  FailedComputeMetricsReplicas  15m   horizontal-pod-autoscaler  invalid metrics (1 invalid out of 1), first error is: failed to get cpu resource metric value: failed to get cpu utilization: unable to get metrics for resource cpu: no metrics returned from resource metrics API
  Warning  FailedGetResourceMetric       15m   horizontal-pod-autoscaler  failed to get cpu utilization: did not receive metrics for targeted pods (pods might be unready)
  Warning  FailedComputeMetricsReplicas  15m   horizontal-pod-autoscaler  invalid metrics (1 invalid out of 1), first error is: failed to get cpu resource metric value: failed to get cpu utilization: did not receive metrics for targeted pods (pods might be unready)
